Guide to the E. E. Wilson Photographic Collection circa 1855-1953
Oregon State University Libraries, Special Collections and Archives Research Center
- Events, circa 1900-1953; Series 3
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453h
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453i
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453j
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0453k
    3 photographic prints; 1 nitrate negative
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0550
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0551
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0552
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0553
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0554
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0555
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0556
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0557
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0558
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0559
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0560
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0561
  - Siletz Indians [?]--4th of July Celebration, 1910; P101:0562
  - Theatrical productions, circa 1900; P101:0621
  - Theatrical productions, circa 1900; P101:0622
- Oregon Agricultural College, circa 1890-1950; Series 4
  Series 4 is comprised of photographs taken on the Oregon Agricultural College (OAC) campus during the late 19th century and early 20th century. The photos capture campus buildings and scenes, class sessions, and students.
  - 1907 class bench and senior grove, P101:0547
  - Aerial view of Corvallis showing Mitchell Playhouse, Education Hall, and Benton Hall, circa 1905; P101:0504
  - Apperson Hall, circa 1905; P101:0494
  - Armory and view of windmill at Wilson house, circa 1900; P101:0512
  - Benton Hall, circa 1895; P101:0507
  - Benton Hall, circa 1900; P101:0492
    2 photographic prints; 1 4x5 glass negative
  - Benton Hall, P101:0543
  - Benton Hall and Education Hall, P101:0539
  - Benton Hall and Education Hall, P101:0540
  - Benton Hall and Wilson house, P101:0513
  - Benton Hall, Benton Annex, and Apperson Hall, circa 1895; P101:0499
    1 photographic print; 1 5x8 glass negative
  - Benton Hall, home of Wilson and Withycombe homes in snow, circa 1890; P101:0511
  - Botany class with Moses Craig, 1890; P101:0495
    3 photographic prints; 1 5x8 glass negative
  - Caged bird in classroom [?], circa 1900; P101:0592b
  - Class in pruning [?], students spraying, circa 1900; P101:0525
  - Classroom instruction--Dairy Husbandry, circa 1900; P101:0594
  - Classroom instruction--Farm Management [?], circa 1900; P101:0584
  - Classroom instruction--Farm Management [?], circa 1900; P101:0588
    1 broken glass negative
  - Classroom instruction--Farm Management [?], circa 1900; P101:0589
  - Classroom instruction--Industrial Arts, circa 1900; P101:0583
  - Classroom instruction--Industrial Arts, circa 1900; P101:0585
  - Classroom instruction--Industrial Arts, circa 1900; P101:0586
  - Classroom instruction--Mathematics, circa 1900; P101:0587
  - Classroom instruction--Mathematics, circa 1900; P101:0590
  - Classroom instruction--Mathematics, circa 1900; P101:0593a
  - Classroom instruction--Soils, circa 1900; P101:0591
  - Classroom instruction--Soils, circa 1900; P101:0592a
  - Classroom instruction--Soils, circa 1900; P101:0593b
  - Cooking class, circa 1890; P101:0500
  - Corvallis College building, 5th Street, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:0183
  - Drawing class with Berchtold, circa 1890; P101:0489
    2 photographic prints (cyanotype)
  - Education Hall, P101:0542
  - Education Hall and paths leading to it, P101:0544
  - Education Hall looking toward Agriculture Hall, P101:0546
  - Fairbanks Hall, circa 1895; P101:0501
  - Fairbanks Hall with cadets on balcony, circa 1892; P101:0496
  - Foundry, circa 1890; P101:0506
  - Fulton, John [?], Leon Louis, and Erma Laurence in college greenhouse, circa 1890; P101:0409b
  - Fulton, John [?], Leon Louis, and Erma Laurence in college greenhouse, P101:0503
  - House of Wilson Family on Oregon Agricultural College campus, P101:0490
    1 photographic print 1 4x5 glass negative
  - Laurence, Erma, in college greenhouse, circa 1895; P101:0322
  - Looking west toward Fairbanks Hall from Benton Hall [?], circa 1895; P101:0498
  - Lower campus looking toward Apperson Hall, P101:0545
  - Lower campus, military cadets firing cannon, circa 1900; P101:0446
  - Machine shop, circa 1895; P101:0526
  - Machine shop, circa 1895; P101:0527
  - Mechanical Engineering Lab, Industrial Arts, 1900; P101:0452
  - Mechanical Hall after fire, September 28, 1898; P101:0516a
  - Mechanical Hall after fire, September 28, 1898; P101:0516b
  - Mechanical Hall after fire, September 28, 1898; P101:0517a
  - Mechanical Hall after fire, September 28, 1898; P101:0517b
  - Memorial Union, Oregon State College, circa 1950; P101:1308
  - OAC cadet, circa 1890; P101:0778
  - OAC tablet, P101:1281
    1 photographic print; 1 broken glass negative
  - Paleontology lab, Apperson Hall, Alpha Hall, circa 1895; P101:0548
  - Path on campus, looking east to "Lady of the Fountain", P101:0541
  - View of lower campus and Corvallis from Education Hall [?], circa 1905; P101:0493
  - Wilson, E.E. and Erma Laurence on lawn behind Benton Hall, circa 1900; P101:0791
  - Wilson, E.E., standing with bicycle outside Benton hall, circa 1900; P101:0508
  - Young woman in college greenhouse, circa 1890; P101:0502
- Oregon Coast, circa 1890-1920; Series 5
  Series 5 is comprised of an extensive body of photographs taken on the Oregon coast. Most of these photos document the area around Yaquina Bay and the town of Newport and include images of Oregon coast landmarks, beach scenes, recreational activities, and homes and structures including the Wilson family coastal home.
  - "T.M. Richardson" steamer on Yaquina Bay, circa 1908; P101:1234
  - Beach at Newport and Yaquina head, circa 1910; P101:1301
  - Beach at Newport from Wilson family coast home; driftwood in foreground and Yaquina Head in distance, circa 1900; P101:1194a
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:1031
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:1032
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:1033
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in background, circa 1910; P101:0865
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in background, circa 1910; P101:0866
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in background, circa 1910; P101:0888
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in background, circa 1910; P101:0890
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in background, circa 1910; P101:0891
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in distance, circa 1900; P101:1034
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in distance, circa 1900; P101:1036
  - Beach at Newport, Oregon with Yaquina Head in background, P101:0889
  - Beach houses [?], circa 1910; P101:0951b
  - Beach houses at sunset, circa 1910; P101:0872
  - Beach houses, Newport, Oregon, circa 1910; P101:1255
    3 photographic prints
  - Beach houses, Newport, Oregon, circa 1910; P101:1256
  - Beach houses, Newport, Oregon, circa 1910; P101:1257
    1 photographic print; 6 nitrate negatives
  - Beach near sunset, circa 1900; P101:0947
  - Beach on cliffs, circa 1900; P101:0876
  - Beach scene, circa 1900; P101:1026
  - Blast removing rock at Newport for construction of the jetty, circa 1900; P101:1096
  - Boat at Yaquina Bay, circa 1910; P101:0893
  - Boat construction, circa 1900; P101:0600
  - Boat cruising in Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1102
  - Boat dock at Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:0892
  - Boat dock on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:0984
  - Boat in river or Yaquina Bay, circa 1910; P101:1204
  - Boat in Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1272
  - Boat on shore of Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1115
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1004
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1027
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1028
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1030
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1113
    1 photographic print; 1 5x7 glass negative
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1114
    2 photographic prints; 1 5x7 glass negative; 1 nitrate negative
  - Boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1118
  - Boat with three men on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1104a
  - Boats on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1101
  - Buoy in Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:0979
  - Camp at Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:1294
  - Cattle grazing near coast, circa 1900; P101:0877
  - Cave on the Oregon coast, P101:1070
  - Coast and mountain scene, P101:0946
  - Coast and mountain scene, P101:0953
  - Coast from Otter Rock [?], circa 1910; P101:0945
  - Coast outing, P101:1203
  - Coast scene, circa 1915; P101:0938
  - Coast scene, circa 1915; P101:0939
  - Coast scene, P101:0929
  - Coast scene, P101:0932
  - Coast scene, P101:0944
  - Coast scene, P101:0954a
  - Coastal beach, circa 1900; P101:0880
  - Coastal homestead, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1078
  - Coastal homestead, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1079a
  - Coastal scene, circa 1910; P101:0951a
  - Cow grazing on Oregon coast, P101:0955
  - Cows grazing along coast [?], P101:1024
  - Entrance to Yaquina Bay, 1920; P101:1038
    1 photographic print (color postcard)
  - Farmhouse near coast, P101:1092
  - Fence at top of cliff along coast, circa 1900; P101:0881
  - Fence at top of cliff along coast, circa 1900; P101:0882
  - Gathering at Nye Beach, circa 1910; P101:1077
  - Group in boat on Yaquina Bay [?], P101:1120
  - Group of women sitting on rocks on beach, circa 1910; P101:1180
  - Group on beach below Yaquina Head Lighthouse, circa 1890s; P101:1116
  - Group picnicking near coast, circa 1910; P101:1200
  - Group picnicking on shore of Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1123
  - Group picnicking on shore of Yaquina Bay [?], P101:1117
  - House near Yaquina Bay [?], P101:1095
  - House next to beach, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1088
  - House next to beach, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1097
  - House overlooking Nye Beach, P101:1081a
  - House overlooking Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1081b
  - Houses near coast, circa 1900; P101:1082
  - Houses near coast, circa 1900; P101:1083
  - Houses near coast, circa 1900; P101:1084
  - Houses near coast, circa 1900; P101:1085
  - Houses near coast, circa 1900; P101:1086
  - Houses near coast, P101:1089a
  - Jump-Off Joe, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1035
  - Jump-Off Joe, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1037
  - Jump-Off Joe, Newport, Oregon, circa 1900; P101:1076
  - Lighthouse at Yaquina Head, circa 1900; P101:1074a
  - Lighthouse at Yaquina Head, circa 1900; P101:1074b
  - Lighthouse at Yaquina Head, circa 1900; P101:1075a
  - Man and woman kissing on beach, circa 1900; P101:0689
  - Man and woman on rocks on beach, circa 1900; P101:1254
  - Man and woman walking along beach, circa 1910; P101:1212
  - Mountains and coast, P101:0903
  - Newport waterfront on Yaquina Bay, circa 1910; P101:1071a
  - Newport waterfront on Yaquina Bay, circa 1910; P101:1071b
  - Nye Beach, circa 1900; P101:1073
  - Nye Beach with Yaquina Head in background, circa 1910; P101:0900
  - Nye Beach, plank walkway, circa 1900; P101:1072
  - Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:1289
  - Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:1290
  - Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:1291
  - Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:1292
  - Oregon coast, circa 1905; P101:1286
  - Oregon coast from Otter Rock, circa 1910; P101:0896
  - Oregon coast from Otter Rock, circa 1910; P101:0897
  - Oregon coast from Otter Rock, circa 1910; P101:0898
  - Oregon coast from Otter Rock, circa 1910; P101:0899
  - Oregon coastline, circa 1905; P101:1288
  - Outing along coast, circa 1910; P101:1104b
  - Outing along coast, circa 1910; P101:1105
  - People in front of beach house, circa 1910; P101:1103
  - People sitting at base of cliff, Oregon coast, circa 1910; P101:1079b
  - People standing on the beach, circa 1900; P101:1214
  - Railroad track in the Oregon Coast Range, circa 1900; P101:1277
  - Rock archway at coast, circa 1900; P101:1041
  - Small island in Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:0912
  - Stewart, Lois [?] and man on beach, circa 1900; P101:0785
  - Sunset views of surf, circa 1900; P101:0894
  - Sunset views of surf, circa 1900; P101:0895
  - Surf at Oregon coast, circa 1905; P101:1285
  - Surf at Oregon coast, circa 1905; P101:1287
  - Surf on rocks, Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:0869
  - Surf on rocks, Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:0873
  - Surf on rocks, Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:0874
  - Surf on rocks, Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:0875
  - Surf on rocks, Oregon coast, circa 1900; P101:0884
  - Surf on the beach, circa 1900; P101:0913
  - T.M. Richards (boat) providing service between Yaquina and Newport, Oregon, P101:0549
  - Toledo, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:0125a
  - Toledo, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:1271
  - Two men at Nye Beach, Newport, Oregon [?], circa 1905; P101:0788
  - Two men in boat in bay at Newport, Oregon [?], circa 1900; P101:1199
  - Two people in boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1110
  - Two people in boat on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1111
  - Two people on beach, circa 1905; P101:1109a
  - Two people on beach, circa 1905; P101:1109b
  - Two people sitting on rocks on beach, circa 1900; P101:0684
  - Two people walking on the beach, circa 1900; P101:0883
  - Two women on beach, circa 1910; P101:1129
  - Two women on beach, circa 1910; P101:1131
  - Unidentified coast scene, P101:0867
  - Unidentified coast scene, P101:0868
  - Unidentified coast scene, P101:0870
  - Unidentified coast scene, P101:0878
  - Unidentified coast scene, P101:0885
  - Unidentified coast scene, P101:0905
  - Unidentified coastal scene, circa 1910; P101:0914b
  - Unidentified coastal scene, circa 1910; P101:0901
  - Unidentified frame house, circa 1910; P101:0851
  - Unidentified Oregon coast scenes, circa 1910; P101:0906
  - Unidentified Oregon coast scenes, circa 1910; P101:0907
  - Unidentified Oregon coast scenes, circa 1910; P101:0908
  - View of boat anchored near shore, Newport, Oregon [?], circa 1915; P101:1211
  - View of houses and barns on Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1093
  - View of side of house on coast [?], P101:1295
  - Views of people on beach, circa 1910; P101:1213
  - Wallusi (boat) grounded at Yaquina Bay, circa 1900; P101:0461
  - Waves along coast, circa 1915; P101:0948
  - Waves along coast, circa 1915; P101:0949
  - Waves along coast, circa 1915; P101:0950
  - Wilson family house at coast, circa 1915; P101:1195
  - Wilson family house at coast, circa 1915; P101:1196
  - Wilson family house at coast, circa 1915; P101:1197
  - Wilson family house at coast, P101:1194b
  - Wilson, E.E. [?] and woman in horse and carriage, P101:0836
  - Wilson, E.E. and group picnicking on beach, circa 1900; P101:1215
  - Wilson, E.E. and Louis Stewart on beach, circa 1900; P101:0797
  - Wilson, E.E. and others on beach, circa 1910; P101:1106
  - Wilson, E.E. and others on beach, circa 1910; P101:1107
  - Wilson, E.E. and others on beach, circa 1910; P101:1108a
  - Wilson, E.E. and others on beach, circa 1910; P101:1108b
  - Wilson, E.E. on beach, circa 1900; P101:0843
  - Wilson, E.E. on beach, circa 1900; P101:0844
  - Wilson, E.E., and Erma Laurence [?] at coast, P101:0408a
  - Wilson, E.E., and Erma Laurence [?] at coast, P101:0408b
  - Wilson, E.E., and group on porch of beach house [?], circa 1900; P101:0653
  - Wilson, E.E., and others on the Newport waterfront [?], circa 1910; P101:1268
  - Wilson, E.E., and woman walking on beach, circa 1905; P101:1284
  - Wilson, E.E., lying on log, Oregon coast, circa 1905; P101:1283
  - Wilson, E.E., on ship off Oregon coast [?], P101:0395a
  - Wilson, E.E., on ship off Oregon coast [?], P101:0395b
  - Wilson, E.E., with group in camp at coast, circa 1900; P101:1293
  - Wilson, Lewis F., on beach, circa 1900; P101:0424
  - Windblown tree on Oregon coast, circa 1910; P101:0887
  - Woman and two children on bank of river, P101:1193
  - Woman standing on beach, circa 1900; P101:0690
  - Woman standing on beach, circa 1910; P101:0702
  - Woman standing on beach looking out at ocean, circa 1910; P101:1112b
  - Women sitting on beach below cliff, circa 1910; P101:1205
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:0941
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:0942
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:0943
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:0952
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:0976
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1900; P101:1029
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:0871
  - Yaquina Bay [?], circa 1910; P101:1039
  - Yaquina Head from Agate Beach area, circa 1910; P101:0902
- Outdoor Recreation and Nature Scenes, circa 1890-1945; Series 6
  Series 6 is comprised of more than 400 images documenting outdoor scenes and activities. Subjects include picnics, camping trips, hunting, fishing, boating, and other outdoor recreation. The series also includes numerous scenic view of Diamond Lake, Crater Lake National Park, the Willamette River, Yellowstone National Park, and locations, many of which are unidentified.
  - "Roberts" boat on river, circa 1900; P101:0261
  - Alder trees [?], circa 1910; P101:0921
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0249
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0250
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0251
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0252
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0253
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0254a
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0254b
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0255a
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0255b
  - Alsea Fish Hatchery, circa 1940; P101:0256
  - Automobile on forest road, circa 1915; P101:1274
  - Bed of Whiskey Creek below Benton Mine, August 5, 1939; P101:1303
  - Bicycle trip to Cardwell Hill with John B. Horner (second from left), 1901; P101:1273
  - Birds mounted on wall, P101:0092
  - Birds mounted on wall, P101:0093
  - Border collie, circa 1905; P101:0089
  - Bouquet of flowers and leaves, P101:0007
  - Bouquets of daffodils, P101:0005
  - Bouquets of daffodils, P101:0006
  - Bridge, P101:1269
  - Bridge over river, circa 1900; P101:1001
  - Burned forest area in front of mountain, P101:1044
  - Cabin, circa 1910; P101:0859
  - Cage, P101:0053
  - Camp, circa 1900; P101:1151
  - Camp among douglas firs, circa 1900; P101:1184
  - Camp by lake, circa 1900; P101:1185
  - Camp by lake in mountains, circa 1900; P101:1161
  - Camp by lake in mountains, circa 1900; P101:1163
  - Camp in forest, circa 1910; P101:1143
  - Camp in forest, circa 1920; P101:1226
  - Camp kitchen with women and children, circa 1900; P101:1178
  - Camp kitchen with women and children, circa 1900; P101:1179
  - Campsite, circa 1900; P101:0862a
  - Campsite, circa 1900; P101:0862b
  - Campsite, circa 1900; P101:0862c
  - Canoe on mountain lake, P101:1126
  - Canoe on river bank, P101:1128
  - Child fishing in stream, circa 1910; P101:1202
  - Child with rake in field, P101:1130
  - Chinook salmon, P101:0022
  - Clouds, P101:0618
    2 4x5 glass negatives
  - Coming upstream on the Rogue River toward Whiskey Creek, August 1, 1939; P101:1305
  - Crater Lake, P101:092
  - Crater Lake National Park, circa 1940; P101:0247
  - Crater Lake National Park, circa 1940; P101:0248
  - Crater Lake National Park--Crater Lake National Park, circa 1940; P101:0244
  - Crater Lake National Park--Crater Lake National Park, circa 1940; P101:0246
  - Crater Lake National Park--Lake, circa 1935; P101:0273
  - Crater Lake National Park--Sandstone formations, circa 1935; P101:0267
  - Crater Lake National Park--Sandstone formations, circa 1935; P101:0268
  - Crater Lake National Park--Valley, circa 1935; P101:0269
  - Crater Lake National Park--Valley, circa 1935; P101:0274
  - Crater Lake National Park--Valley, circa 1935; P101:0275
  - Crater Lake National Park--View northwest from Wizard Island [?], circa 1940; P101:0242
  - Crater Lake National Park--View northwest from Wizard Island [?], circa 1940; P101:0243
  - Crater Lake National Park--View of lake to the north [?], circa 1940; P101:0241
  - Crater Lake National Park--View of lake to the north [?], circa 1940; P101:0245
  - Crown Point, Columbia River Gorge, P101:1367
  - Daffodils, P101:0002
  - Daffodils, P101:0003
  - Daffodils, P101:0008
  - Dead birds hanging., P101:0090a
  - Dead birds on counter., P101:0091
  - Dead trees, mountains in background, circa 1900; P101:0998
  - Deer hunt, circa 1900; P101:1233
    3 photographic prints; 2 nitrate negatives
  - Delta at mouth of Whiskey Creek, looking up the Rogue River, August 7, 1939; P101:1304
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:0181
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:0999
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1047
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1048
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1051
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1052
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1053
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1054
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1055
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1056
  - Diamond Lake, circa 1930; P101:1057
  - Diamond Lake [?], circa 1910; P101:0924
  - Diamond Lake, Metolius, circa 1930; P101:0178
  - Diamond Lake, Metolius, circa 1930; P101:0179
  - Diamond Lake, Metolius, circa 1930; P101:0180
  - Dog and pheasants, P101:0079
  - Dog and pheasants, P101:0080
  - Dog and pheasants, P101:0081
  - Dog and pheasants, P101:0082
  - Dog in yard, P101:0086
  - Dog lying on hillside, P101:0084
  - Dog on steps, P101:0085
  - Dog perched on a garden cart, P101:0088
  - Dog perched on wooden box, P101:0083
  - Dog with a man, P101:0087
  - Dog with pheasants, circa 1900; P101:0582
  - Driftwood on rocks on beach, circa 1900; P101:0886
  - Ducks crossing barnyard, circa 1905; P101:0090b
    6 photographic prints; 1 broken glass negative
  - Ducks mounted on wall, P101:0094
  - Ducks mounted on wall, P101:0095
  - E.E. Wilson with mounted deer head, circa 1900; P101:0026
  - Eastern Oregon, P101:0463
  - Fallen log across stream, circa 1900; P101:1015
  - Ferry crossing river, Corvallis, Oregon, circa 1915; P101:1275
  - Finger Rock, circa 1890; P101:1067
  - Finger Rock, circa 1900; P101:1068
  - Finger Rock, circa 1900; P101:1069
  - Fish on grass, P101:0018
  - Forest and mountains, P101:1045
  - Forest and mountains, P101:1046
  - Forest camp site, circa 1900; P101:1135
  - Forest camp site, circa 1900; P101:1136
  - Forest path, circa 1900; P101:0960
  - Forest path, circa 1900; P101:0962
  - Forest path, circa 1900; P101:1000
  - Forest reflected in pool of water, circa 1910; P101:0981
  - Forest river, circa 1900; P101:0974a
  - Forest river, P101:0977
  - Forest road, circa 1920; P101:0995
  - Forest road near Diamond Lake [?], circa 1930; P101:1061
  - Forest scene, P101:0940
  - Forest scene from stream bed [?], circa 1900; P101:0956
  - Forest scene from stream bed [?], circa 1900; P101:0959
  - Four men in camp, circa 1900; P101:1080
  - Group in camp by stream, P101:1169
  - Group of men and women on rocks, circa 1900; P101:0674
  - Group of men on hike [?], circa 1910; P101:1150
  - Group of people camping, P101:1124
  - Group of people camping, P101:1125
  - Group of people camping, P101:1181
  - Group picnicking on large log, circa 1900; P101:1167
  - Group sitting at camp table, circa 1900; P101:1172
  - Group sitting at camp table, circa 1900; P101:1186
  - Group sitting in camp with dogs, circa 1900; P101:1187
  - Group standing in front of tent, circa 1900; P101:1174
  - Group standing in front of tent, circa 1900; P101:1188